<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chapliboy</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on chapliboy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 10:06:06 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>cluegrid</title>
      <link>/projects/cluegrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 10:06:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/cluegrid/</guid>
      <description>cluegrid is a web app to solve crosswords with a friend
Link to app
Link to source
cluegrid was build in elm. It uses websockets for the real time collaborative aspects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nimbus</title>
      <link>/projects/nimbus2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 10:06:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/nimbus2018/</guid>
      <description>Nimbus2018 is a minesweeper bot.
   Lightning talk at PyCon India 2018
Screen recording of the bot in action
At the top of the leaderboard.
Link to source
Nimbus 2018 is a bot that solves minesweeper. It was written in python. It uses PyAutoGui for screen capture, and mouse movements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a bit about me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 21:56:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m Samarth. Or Sam. Or chapliboy.
I like building things.
Yup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Adding Responsiveness to a Web App</title>
      <link>/posts/responsive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 21:56:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/responsive/</guid>
      <description>The first rule of responsive web design is often shouted off the rooftops.
Design for mobile first. Always mobile first. I know this rule. I&#39;ve heard it several times. I&#39;ve been rudely awoken from my sleep because of all the rooftop screaming. So what do you think I did when I was building my web based crossword app? I didn&#39;t even bother considering for mobile..
Maybe I am a rebel. Or maybe I just didn&#39;t have enough faith in my ability to actually see a project through, and rather than getting stuck in the quagmire of figuring what exactly it means to design for mobile first, I decided I&#39;d rather just dive in, and figure out all those other things along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minesweeper. Another Love Story</title>
      <link>/posts/minesweeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 21:15:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/minesweeper/</guid>
      <description>Originally published on Medium
Her face was bathed in white light as she leaned closer to the monitor. “If this is a 1, then one of these two must be a mine…” she thought aloud, her fingers touching the screen.
“And if you look at this tile…” he gently prodded.
“This must be the mine!” she shrieked, her face now glowing brighter than the monitor.
She was playing minesweeper. And she was loving it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>